alright last year I was actually
on this stage and uh...
去年我来这里讲过, 等下我直接播放好叻
and I gave a little talk actually
I'm just gonna play quick uh...
excerpts of of that right
去年我来这里讲过, 等下我直接播放好叻
now
I talked about
我讲的下一个话题是关于
web development workflow
Web开发工作流程
because I think over the past two
years in particular there's been a
lot of tools that
我认为这两年有很多新的工具
we've got in as developers to increase
our productivity, reduce our stress
可以加快开发者的工作流程
putting them together in kind of a
work flow that make sense has been
an interesting challenge
如何把他们融合在一起是一个有趣的挑战
so I'm gonna walk through what
my approaches has been and some of
the approaches I've seen other
所以我来谈谈我还有其他人是如何做的
developers doing
uh... first thing i should point out
先说一下
please try and pay no attention to the
enormous rhinoceros genetalia behind
(这句话我不翻译啦)
me
it is distracting
大家不要为了它而分心哟
it is very distracting
um...
but anyway so yes last year i talked
about the javascript workflow of
不管怎样, 去年我谈了2013 JS开发工作流程
um... so i've figured it would be kind
of good to revisit that now that it's
我觉得应该回顾一下, 毕竟现在就是2013
2013 so this is the javascript
authoring workflow of now
um...yeah
a few things I touched on last year
uh... just quick little excerpts
再上一段视频嘞
things here and there
(开播了)
so I think having realtime feedback
我认为有实时的反馈很重要
is an important thing live recompilation
and live reload now massages ?
比如实时更新, 还有实时编译等
here
the sass final
你看这里, 编译后的Sass
the next is source maps
然后我们谈谈source maps
okay just
(okay, 大家回神了)
quick little
bits and bobs of technologies um... buzz
words but all useful things
去年演讲中提到的这几个流行词
and last year I kind of showed kind of putting
these together kind of disparate
有大概谈谈他们是怎么结合在一起
technologies to kind of come into
a workflow that kind of works together
uh... but on the chrome dev tools team we've been
之后我们Chrome 开发者工具团队就一直在想如何
thinking about this and figured out how we can
make this into a more cohesive workflow
把他们更好的融入到开发者工具里面
and I wanna show you some of the
features uh...
今天就来展示一下成果
that have come out of that work
the first up is called workspaces
第一个是Workspaces
um... but um...
噢噢
uh... this is embarrassing uh... so
just bear with me I'm gonna fix this now
等下个...让我修修
just dadan da
(哼歌中...)
just kill this actually I'm gonna
come to my editor
让我把这个干掉, 然后去我的编辑器
let's make some
把新的样式放在这里
room for that so that we can put in some
new styles uh... I don't need this width
哒哒哒...不需要这个width
that should fix that I can turn off this box shadow
然后关掉这个box-shadow
Get a line height, that looks about right-ish
加个line-height, 这样就差不多了
and font size
再来个font-size
uh...
alright, let's bring these changes over to my editor
酱紫, 来到我的编辑器
change on disk reload
所有改动立刻浮现哈
sure sure, oh
oh, all right
as you can see here
nice dev tools is doing this work for
me so i'm making changes in the styles
panel
it's going to bring these back to disk
so let's say I actually wanna add something back over
here inside sublime and let's see
we'll do 1px 1px 10px and
white
um... just hit save and come over
here, yeah, that's that's
looks pretty pretty good, but
I'm gonna go with black instead
yes that's sharp okay cool
styles are looking good but we still have
Whoops
um...
so this is a HTML slide deck but
I'm using markdown for the contents
so let's
edit the markdown I'm gonna hit the Command + O
and it bring up slides.md
and uh... here
is that typo just change that to
lowercase and hit Command + S to save
and refresh
looking good... cool nice
so this is workspaces
workspaces allows me to bring in
folders on my system into the dev tools
and edit it what the dev tool is going to do is
map this to what's coming over the wire
so i can i make full backend and serving up
this content
dev tools going map the resources so
that when i make changes to things on
screen it's gonna be able to make these
changes to what's persistent on disk as well
I can edit everything this is you know
this is mark down here the dev tool team
itself actually edit the c++ bindings for
dev tool inside of dev tools
um...
style changes as they make them over
here in the styles panel they persist all these
changes are kept on persistent disk
I can edit anywhere
full undo redo, especially here
uh... man this is great because I'm able
to maintain my context and not keep
switching between two separate things
just do it all in one place
uh...
all right, next thing up
sass this was something that i
mentioned last year and a lot of people
have been asking about this I want to
bring you up-to-date with how this works
inside of dev tools now
alright to do this I would bring up
uh... version of HTML5 please
and this is looking good
but I wanna actually try experimenting
with this guy right here this little use
badge
so uh... open up the dev tools you know what
I'm gonna try to change the color of it
all right so here we are
that's good
the uh... uses got a background box-shadow
and border-right
green and getting a little getting darker in
the greens as it goes down
so if we want to try to change the color
I'm really keen on indigo lately
uh... I don't know why, it's cool
but that really don't work out well so hot
hmm...Command + Z
good yes uh...
so if i click through the actual style on CSS
those of you are SASSies will notice this
looks like compiled uncompressed
CSS coming from the styles panel compiler
so what i should really be doing is authoring in SASS
so let's turn that on
we go the dev tool setting and bring up
experiments and turn on Sass, cool
refresh the page
bring back up the dev tools
and go back to my selection
now the first thing that you're gonna
notice is pretty small
is that here against the usual you're
seeing the location in the sass file
where this is coming from
so Imma click through on that
all right cool so here we are in my sass file
and uh... looks like use is actually using a mixin
uh... but i wanted to change that color
so we're gonna have to dig a little bit deeper
so i come back over here and I hit Command
and you can now see that these things
are a little clickable so I'm gonna
Command + click on background
and we jump into the extends file where
our mixins are defined
background box-shadow border-right and yeap
the color that's coming in
right here is in fact is being
darkened as it comes down
all right that makes sense
but again I need to change that color
and I come back to elements and command click
on the color itself
all right
so now we are over here in our
in our _vars.scss file
and the cursor is placed immediately
where this variable was defined
so the use one is right here and
this is that green and um...
uh... so i want to try it as being
indigo, Command + S
yeah...nice
it's pretty good but honestly that green
color worked the best
so just command + Z to back my way to that green
cool, all right so this is done with no chrome
extensions at all so this is just straight up dev tools
in fact
the only thing that I have going on in
addition to uh... the Sass support and
workspaces
is I do have
a Sass watch daemon just watching
these things and recompile in
on-the-fly
but dev tools is doing the work of
bringing in the new changes as they come in
so we have full traceability from my css
the selectors, properties, and
variables back to the original sass
sources whether came from a mixin or a
variable or whatever
this is actually enabled by
source maps I talked about it last year
source maps are javascript this is the same
technology just for css
uh... and this was contributed
uh... to the sass compiler core by the
dev tools team and I should mention that
um... if you're not sass user and you
like stylus or less
uh... the limitations completely agnostic so
once less or stylus gets support to
create the source maps
it's gonna work the exact same way
and a full automatic reload of the stylesheet
as changes coming
pretty nice
so these changes combined really change things
up dev tool can become my editor
uh... i think it's really powerful
cuz I'm getting this real time feedback as i'm
typing as I'm making changes
I see the style changes as I type them
out whether in css or
sass
is persistent to disk
by way of uh... workspaces
if I'm doing javascript I can edit that and
it's re-evaluated on-the-fly it's
patched up to send to V8 and it
just takes care of it great when you're
doing any sort of campus work ?
uh...
in this also cool because when
you author code and you seem to debug ?
environment you can place break point right
about the same place which leads to a great
cohesive environment, all right
last year I also brought a package
management but I covered it in kind of
hint wavy way I'm gonna play that
package management is
something that in a year from now
we're gonna have really robust package
management tooling infrastructure and a
lot of packages in the community right
now it's kind of still finding its
foothold but we will be seeing some more
things coming up soon I think
yeah uh... was actually just a few weeks
before the release of bower
bower is a package manager project that
I have been involved in since the beginning
and it's really been taken off fantastic
thing uh... the community in the
registry have kind of blown up this is a
view of all the components
that are in bower and it's now up to a
little over twenty-two hundred
components available in the registry
really great for you as a user and
whenever you want to pull something
and it has dependencies it works great
also great for the ecosystem because it
means that we're able to build upon each
other's work in a lot more of a cohesive way
if you want to get up to speed on this
there was a great presentation about
bower down in google IO just two weeks ago
dan hoverd showed off a lot of great
stuff including a really nice workflow
using bower and requirejs also yeoman
and grunt
to create this great experience of using
package management something that you
might expect from another language
uh... but having it here inside of
uh... javascript for the front end
alright wanna come back to performance
and talking about performance at a
javascript conference
uh... i might talk about javascript
performance
but it's
good to keep in mind that
javascript is not
kind of
it's not always the best target
these are slides from actually from the
IE team back when they're released
IE8
but this stuff is as true it was then as it is now
up here we have they took a look at the top one hundred sites and saw where
IE was spending its time
and just sixteen percent of its time was spent
in javascript
rest of it in layout rendering formatting
and here for ajax heavy sites like
javascript heavy sites like uh... gmail
google maps
uh... just still a fraction
so javascript is often a small
fraction of the overall performance
picture
so if you want to find out how to make
your app your site fast
I recommend you take a look at the timeline
inside the chrome dev tools so
uh... I'm gonna show that to you now
all right
so this is a kind of info graphic parallax site
it's pretty cool
and I'm just gonna scroll through it so
you get a chance to see what's going on so as I
scroll down I got this orange
circle bubbly guy and these
circles over here where is comes to
some awesome physics explosion
uh...
and then come down here we have a parallax
effect it's pretty cool I keep going down
and uh...keep going down
these white little dots form these gride
and just take over the place
and that's about it, all right
let's come back up and open up dev tool this time
and drag it down to the bottom
open up the timeline
and i'm gonna start recording
just hit Command + D
It's kind of quick
and then I'm just gonna scroll through
the same stuff
dudu dudu
all right, what's really cool about that
is we get for you the
performance of the this page kind of in a
narrative
it starts off at the beginning it's pretty chill
and then we move on to the sections here
where there's a lot of green
now this is up at the top
where we are building out this kind of orange
explosion of circles and the green is time spent in paint
and here we are painting the entire
page on every single frame
it's taking a good amount of time
then going into this section where there's a lot of yellow
and this is javascript executing
that is when we're hitting
uh... this little physics action right here
that it's pretty quiet for the section
in the middle we are hitting our target
frame budget of sixty FPS mostly frames stay underneath that
for the most part
and then down at the bottom we kind of have
this cacophony of colors
a lot of things happening as this kind of
white things exploding
uh... both painting javascript and also
a good amount of a purple layout here
uh... is going on
but timeline is giving us this overall
view of finding where our bomb are ?
of each section so we can deal with a bit
more precise in how we adjust these
performance issues
so if I wanna look into
this section right here I'm gonna do that
so let's see right here
uh... and I want to get a better idea of
this javascript performance
so let's do that
I'm gonna go over to profiles and collect a CPU profile
Hit Command + E
and
it's probably good
and now if I come over here and uh...
so this you should be used to
kind of the aggregate view of everything that's going on
and it is telling me kind of here are
all the things that happened information
well what it's not doing it is
giving it to me and kind of this view
I could see frame by frame
what happened bit by a bit
so this is we found we can
address and also give you a better idea as
far as
of visualization of this action
so I want to show it to you a new feature
and it's called the flame chart
uh...all right
so here we have the flame chart
we're able to identify kind of at
time scale across time how things are
changing in this case it's actually pretty consistent
um... frame by frame looks like it's
mostly executing the same javascript
it would change color if not
uh... and then it also
drill in so this is one frame in particular
and
in this case uh...
width is time
and height is call stacks so height's not too important
but umm
if I wanna look in I can see a few things let's say
uh... here
looks like D3 is kind of running
the show all my time to spend inside D3
we got some insert child so it's doing some SVG inserting
uh... and then we have this quadtree view
quadtree view quadtree view quadtree view
insert child
but also inserting attribute function just
settings new attributes in the SVG at the
end of the frame
this is a seven milliseconds in this case
which is a considerable amount of time
to happen every single frame
but this visualization is giving me a great view as far as what is soaking up this
time and what should i address first
so that's the new flamed chart
you can check it out in chrome canary today
uh... we also have a canvas profiling
experiment that I want to show to you now
so this here just this webGL aquarium
and Imma open up the dev tools
and take a canvas profile so it's
gonna record single canvas frame and
it's recording all the calls that
contributed to that frame
and poke through all the draw calls
one-by-one and just hitting the down arrow
on the keyboard walking through
how the scene was actually drawn so you can see
the fishes come in and the shark come in
the the the ball kind of come in
and everything else
and then you open up the draw calls
and see all the function calls
that contributed to that draw
and go back to the sources
so this is cool but this is a platform
this is we are able to record and replay
canvas and webGL action
uh... but really where we go from here
is up to you and so please wrench in
your feedback in kind of what you would
like to see next as far as a canvas profiler
all right I'm gonna wrap-up with five key
dev tools performance features
first up continuous repaint mode
if you're in the timeline you see a lot
of time spent inside green painting
then you probably wanna head over t
continuous repaint mode what it's gonna do
is tell the browser
hey paint the page again and again and again
and what this allows you to do is turn off elements and styles
and figure out what is contributing to the
amount of time that it takes to paint
the page
uh... and this is able to uh... to let
you find out what's contributing what you
could adjust uh... it the changes so
it's a it's a little tough to
given aggregate view of
but you're able to find out exactly
what's contributing there
and also the FPS Meter um... which
gives you a good view of how fast you're
sending updates to the screen
so in addition to showing the frames per second
we also have min and max in that view
and a histogram
also the GPU memory so you can see how much memory
is being used by the current tab, how
much is allocated if you have a lot of
heavy imagery you're going to constantly
evicting things out of the GPU
memory which is probably gonna soak up a good amount of GPU performance
uh... next up show paint rects and layer borders
these are available as settings inside
dev tools
really great at identifying paint
issues so you might be repainting
the entire page on every single scroll
you don't wannna to do that and this is
going to show you a visual view of that
happening really fast in this case uh...
it looks like
this div was just repainted and we have
uh... a layer over here with the gold border
it's actually the scrollbar which
chrome actually composites right on
top of the page
the object allocation trackers a brand
new tool if you're doing a lot of memory
analysis this is going to key for you so
you hit a do recording and it's gonna take
continual heap snapshots over time
that's how it identifies drillin on one specific part
to see what objects were allocated in that section
and what they retain size and what they
retaining tree which is great even try
to identify where your memory is coming
from and where it's going
lastly layout thrashing back in uh...
this timeline here
we see a good amount of time spent in
layout
and here we're able to identify a
bunch of stuff have you had a DOM heavy
web applications
you might see something like this where
you doing layout and layout and layout
and there's no paint you do it all this
work and you're asking browser to do all this
work
and the users never seen a lot of it and
this is a problem dev tools is gonna
tell you that with this little icon that there is
possible performance bottleneck
uh... this is also gonna give you
a lot of other useful information too
the amount of nodes that need layouts
the tree size the scope
and also a full call stack for why the
layout was invalidated why it was forced to
conjoint as functions and find exactly
why things were caused maybe you're gonna need
to change some things around
so a lot of details and this is key to getting good performance on web
applications
okay that's a lot of stuff the chrome tools documentation
has recently got a bunch of
new updates covering these things
and a bunch more including remote
debugging everything i show today uh...
is available as you remote debug your
phone uh... so it's a really powerful
setup and I encourage you to check that out
uh... everything I should today is also
available in canary some of them behind
experiments but I encourage you to check out
try things holler at me and tell me what
you like what you don't like uh... and
uh... it'd be good
but thank you guys very much
00:00:01,510 - > 00:00:06,939
实际上，我是去年没事
在这个阶段，呃......
00:00:06,940 - > 00:00:11,130
我给聊一会儿。实际上
我只是要打出快速呃......
该权利的摘录
00:00:11,130 - > 00:00:16,298
现在
00:00:16,298 - > 00:00:17,390
我谈
00:00:17,390 - > 00:00:19,118
Web开发工作流程
00:00:19,118 - > 00:00:22,448
因为我觉得在过去两年
特别是年已经有
很多工具，
00:00:22,449 - > 00:00:26,609
我们已经有了作为开发商增加
我们的生产效率，减少我们的压力
00:00:26,609 - > 00:00:30,219
把它们放在一起的实物
工作流程，使意义上来讲已经
一个有趣的挑战
00:00:30,219 - > 00:00:33,460
所以我要通过什么走
我的方法已经和一些
我见过的其他方法
00:00:33,460 - > 00:00:34,960
开发商做
00:00:34,960 - > 00:00:36,800
呃...第一件事，我要指出的
00:00:36,799 - > 00:00:40,659
请尝试不注意
巨大的犀牛genetalia背后
00:00:40,659 - > 00:00:44,919
我
00:00:44,920 - > 00:00:46,070
它是分心
00:00:46,070 - > 00:00:48,289
它是非常分散
00:00:48,289 - > 00:00:49,880
嗯...
00:00:49,880 - > 00:00:54,480
但无论如何，是去年我跟
有关JavaScript的工作流程
00:00:54,479 - > 00:00:55,489
00:00:55,490 - > 00:01:00,240
嗯...所以我估计这将是一种
好重新审视，现在，它是
00:01:00,240 - > 00:01:04,329
2013年，所以这是JavaScript
现在创作的工作流程
00:01:04,329 - > 00:01:07,269
嗯...是啊
00:01:07,269 - > 00:01:11,859
去年的几件事情，我感动
呃...只是快一点摘录
00:01:11,859 - > 00:01:13,239
在这里和那里的东西
00:01:13,239 - > 00:01:15,420
所以我觉得有实时反馈
00:01:15,420 - > 00:01:20,340
是一件重要的事情现场重新编译
现在现场重新按摩？
00:01:20,340 - > 00:01:21,280
这里
00:01:21,280 - > 00:01:22,820
上海社会科学院决赛
00:01:22,819 - > 00:01:24,549
接下来是源地图
00:01:24,549 - > 00:01:25,890
还好，只是
00:01:25,890 - > 00:01:26,849
快速的小
00:01:26,849 - > 00:01:31,829
位和羁绊的技术嗯...蜂鸣器
话，但所有有用的东西，最后
00:01:31,829 - > 00:01:34,549
今年我种表现出一种把
这些一起种不同
00:01:34,549 - > 00:01:36,599
技术，以一种进入
00:01:36,599 - > 00:01:40,688
那种一起工作的工作流程
呃...但铬开发工具团队，我们一直
00:01:40,688 - > 00:01:44,709
思考这个问题想通了，我们如何能够
使之成为一个更具凝聚力的工作流程
00:01:44,709 - > 00:01:48,209
我想告诉你一些
功能呃......
00:01:48,209 - > 00:01:52,869
这方面的工作，已走出
首先是称为工作
00:01:52,870 - > 00:01:55,719
嗯...但是，恩...
00:01:55,719 - > 00:02:00,700
呃...这是令人尴尬的呃...所以
只有忍耐我，我会立即解决这个问题
00:02:00,700 - > 00:02:04,189
只是大胆达
00:02:04,189 - > 00:02:07,700
只要杀了这个实际上我要去
来我的编辑器
00:02:07,700 - > 00:02:08,438
让我们做一些
00:02:08,438 - > 00:02:13,338
空间，这样我们就可以把一些
新的风格呃...我不需要这个宽度
00:02:13,338 - > 00:02:17,229
这应该可以解决，我可以关闭此框阴影
00:02:17,229 - > 00:02:22,488
行高，看起来右侧上下的
00:02:22,489 - > 00:02:23,959
和字体大小
00:02:23,959 - > 00:02:25,769
呃...
00:02:25,769 - > 00:02:30,968
好吧，让我们把这些变化我的编辑
00:02:30,968 - > 00:02:32,289
改变盘重装
00:02:32,289 - > 00:02:35,728
请一定一定哦
00:02:35,729 - > 00:02:37,650
哦，没事
00:02:37,650 - > 00:02:44,650
你可以在这里看到
00:02:45,419 - > 00:02:49,079
很好的开发工具做这个工作
我让我的样式的变化
00:02:49,079 - > 00:02:50,368
面板
00:02:50,368 - > 00:02:54,308
它会带来这些回磁盘
让我们说，其实我想添加的东西回到了
00:02:54,308 - > 00:02:57,838
这里里面崇高，让我们来看看
我们会做1px的1px的10px的
00:02:57,838 - > 00:02:59,258
白
00:02:59,258 - > 00:03:03,608
嗯...刚打救过来
00:03:03,609 - > 00:03:05,120
在这里，是的，就是这样的
00:03:05,120 - > 00:03:09,079
小艾还算不错，但
黑色而不是我要去
00:03:09,079 - > 00:03:11,209
没错，这是尖锐的好吗酷
00:03:11,209 - > 00:03:15,150
样式看起来不错，但我们仍然有
00:03:15,150 - > 00:03:15,989
哎呦
00:03:15,989 - > 00:03:17,558
嗯...
00:03:17,558 - > 00:03:22,539
所以这是一个HTML幻灯片，但
我使用的是降价的内容
00:03:22,539 - > 00:03:23,698
让我们
00:03:23,699 - > 00:03:26,049
编辑降价，我会打命令+ O
00:03:26,049 - > 00:03:28,859
带来了slides.md的
00:03:28,859 - > 00:03:30,729
呃...这里
00:03:30,729 - > 00:03:35,409
错字改变，要
小写和打命令+ S保存
00:03:35,408 - > 00:03:37,388
和刷新
00:03:37,389 - > 00:03:39,789
好看...凉爽的好
00:03:39,788 - > 00:03:42,129
所以这是工作区
00:03:42,129 - > 00:03:47,938
工作区允许我带
在我的系统上的文件夹到开发工具
00:03:47,938 - > 00:03:50,459
编辑什么开发工具是要干什么
00:03:50,459 - > 00:03:54,489
什么是未来的线路上的映射
这样我就可以使完整的后端服务
00:03:54,489 - > 00:03:55,460
此内容
00:03:55,460 - > 00:03:59,180
开发工具的资源映射
当我做出改变的事情
00:03:59,180 - > 00:04:02,969
屏幕上，它会是能够使这些
什么是持久性的，以及在磁盘上的变化
00:04:02,969 - > 00:04:05,968
我可以编辑一切，这是你知道
00:04:05,968 - > 00:04:09,318
这是在这里记下的开发工具团队
本身实际上编辑c + +绑定
内部开发工具开发工具
00:04:09,318 - > 00:04:12,149
00:04:12,149 - > 00:04:13,140
嗯...
00:04:13,139 - > 00:04:16,889
因为他们使他们的风格变化
在“样式”面板中，他们坚持所有这些
00:04:16,889 - > 00:04:19,859
永久性磁盘上保存修改
我可以编辑任何地方
00:04:19,858 - > 00:04:21,878
完全撤消重做，尤其是在这里
00:04:21,879 - > 00:04:24,919
呃...人这是伟大的，因为我能
保持我的背景和跟不上
00:04:24,918 - > 00:04:28,990
两回事之间切换
只是这样做在同一个地方
00:04:28,990 - > 00:04:30,610
呃...
00:04:30,610 - > 00:04:31,740
所有的权利，接下来的事情上涨
00:04:31,740 - > 00:04:35,879
这是上海社会科学院的东西，我
提到去年很多人
00:04:35,879 - > 00:04:39,339
已经问到这个问题，我想
给您带来了最新与如何工作的
00:04:39,339 - > 00:04:41,338
现在里面的开发工具
00:04:41,338 - > 00:04:43,009
好吧做到这一点，我会带起来
00:04:43,009 - > 00:04:46,490
呃... HTML5的版本，请
00:04:46,490 - > 00:04:48,509
这是好看
00:04:48,509 - > 00:04:52,649
但我想尝试
这家伙，这里很少使用
00:04:52,649 - > 00:04:54,378
徽章
00:04:54,379 - > 00:04:59,028
所以，嗯...开放的开发工具，你知道什么
我要去尝试改变它的颜色
00:04:59,028 - > 00:05:01,230
所有的权利，使我们在这里
00:05:01,230 - > 00:05:03,050
这是很好的
00:05:03,050 - > 00:05:07,610
恩...使用了一个背景框阴影
边境右
00:05:07,610 - > 00:05:12,528
绿色和一点点越来越暗
果岭下山
00:05:12,528 - > 00:05:17,050
因此，如果我们想尝试改变颜色
最近我真的很热衷于靛蓝
00:05:17,050 - > 00:05:19,400
呃...我不知道为什么，这很酷
00:05:19,399 - > 00:05:24,500
但事实真的不工作这么热
00:05:24,500 - > 00:05:25,668
嗯......命令+ Z
00:05:25,668 - > 00:05:27,930
好是呵......
00:05:27,930 - > 00:05:31,889
所以，如果我点击通过实际的风格CSS
00:05:31,889 - > 00:05:36,629
那些你会发现这个Sassy族
貌似编译未压缩
00:05:36,629 - > 00:05:38,629
CSS来自样式“面板编译器
00:05:38,629 - > 00:05:42,309
还等什么我真正应该做的是创作，在上海社会科学院
00:05:42,309 - > 00:05:43,759
让我们打开上
00:05:43,759 - > 00:05:50,160
我们去开发工具的设置和造就
萨斯，凉爽的实验和转
00:05:50,160 - > 00:05:51,529
刷新页面
00:05:51,528 - > 00:05:53,168
带回了开发工具
00:05:53,168 - > 00:05:55,418
回到我的选择
00:05:55,418 - > 00:05:58,978
现在的第一件事情，你要去
通知是相当小
00:05:58,978 - > 00:06:03,240
是，在这里你有悖于
看到青菜文件的位置
00:06:03,240 - > 00:06:04,619
这是来自
00:06:04,619 - > 00:06:07,240
所以伊马通过点击
00:06:07,240 - > 00:06:10,348
所有权利凉爽，所以在这里，我们是在我的青菜文件
00:06:10,348 - > 00:06:15,300
呃...使用看起来像使用的实际上是混入
00:06:15,300 - > 00:06:20,270
呃...但我想改变颜色
所以我们要去要挖更深一点点
00:06:20,269 - > 00:06:22,538
等我回来在这里和我打命令
00:06:22,538 - > 00:06:25,899
现在您可以看到，这些东西
有一点可以点击的，所以我要去
00:06:25,899 - > 00:06:27,500
命令+点击背景
00:06:27,500 - > 00:06:31,988
我们跳进扩展文件
我们的混入定义了
00:06:31,988 - > 00:06:34,369
背景框阴影边界权和叶氏
00:06:34,370 - > 00:06:36,718
的颜色来
00:06:36,718 - > 00:06:40,339
这里实际上是被
它归结变黑
00:06:40,339 - > 00:06:41,938
是有道理的所有权利
00:06:41,939 - > 00:06:45,210
但我需要再次改变颜色
我回来元素和命令点击
00:06:45,209 - > 00:06:47,028
本身的颜色
00:06:47,028 - > 00:06:48,158
好的
00:06:48,158 - > 00:06:50,319
所以现在我们在我们这里被过度
00:06:50,319 - > 00:06:51,759
在我们_vars.scss文件
00:06:51,759 - > 00:06:55,559
并且将光标放置在紧接
这个变量被定义
00:06:55,559 - > 00:07:00,199
所以使用的是这里
这是绿色和um ...
00:07:00,199 - > 00:07:02,319
呃...所以我想尝试它作为
00:07:02,319 - > 00:07:06,460
靛蓝，命令+ S
00:07:06,459 - > 00:07:13,459
啊......不错
00:07:15,769 - > 00:07:20,149
这是相当不错，但说实话，绿色
颜色效果最好
00:07:20,149 - > 00:07:24,149
所以只是命令+ Z来还给我的方式，绿色
00:07:24,149 - > 00:07:27,968
酷，所有的权利所以这是做无铬
在所有的扩展，因此开发工具，这仅仅是直线上升
00:07:27,968 - > 00:07:29,019
其实
00:07:29,019 - > 00:07:33,778
唯一的事情，我已经打算在
除了呵...的萨斯支持和
00:07:33,778 - > 00:07:34,899
工作区
00:07:34,899 - > 00:07:36,348
是我做的有
00:07:36,348 - > 00:07:40,738
只是看着一个萨斯手表守护
这些事情，并重新编译
00:07:40,738 - > 00:07:42,288
飞
00:07:42,288 - > 00:07:46,688
但开发工具是做什么工作
带来的新变化，因为他们在
00:07:46,689 - > 00:07:50,129
所以我们有充分的可追溯性，从我的CSS
选择器，属性和
00:07:50,129 - > 00:07:53,919
变量恢复到原来的青菜
来源是否来自一个混入或
00:07:53,918 - > 00:07:55,478
变量或任何
00:07:55,478 - > 00:07:58,808
这实际上是启用
源地图我谈到去年
00:07:58,809 - > 00:08:02,879
源地图的javascript，这是相同的
只是CSS技术
00:08:02,879 - > 00:08:04,660
呃...这提供的
00:08:04,660 - > 00:08:08,420
呃...青菜编译内核
开发工具团队，我应该指出，
00:08:08,420 - > 00:08:11,580
嗯...如果你不是青菜用户，并且您
像手写笔或更少
00:08:11,579 - > 00:08:17,248
呃...限制完全不可知的，所以
一次小于或手写笔得到支持
00:08:17,249 - > 00:08:19,110
创建源地图
00:08:19,110 - > 00:08:21,088
它是怎么工作的方式不尽相同
00:08:21,088 - > 00:08:23,699
和一个完整的自动重装的样式表
00:08:23,699 - > 00:08:25,639
为改变未来
00:08:25,639 - > 00:08:26,699
相当不错的
00:08:26,699 - > 00:08:31,679
所以结合这些变化真的改变的事情
开发工具可以成为我的编辑
00:08:31,678 - > 00:08:35,389
呃...我认为这是真正强大
因为我得到这个作为我的实时反馈
00:08:35,389 - > 00:08:37,129
我打字更改
00:08:37,129 - > 00:08:40,370
我看到我键入他们的风格变化
是否在CSS或
00:08:40,370 - > 00:08:41,310
上海社会科学院
00:08:41,309 - > 00:08:43,750
持久化到磁盘
00:08:43,750 - > 00:08:46,799
呃...工作区
00:08:46,799 - > 00:08:50,339
如果我做的javascript我可以编辑，
它的重新评估在飞
00:08:50,340 - > 00:08:54,080
发送到V8和它修补
只是需要照顾它伟大的，当你
00:08:54,080 - > 00:08:55,830
做任何形式的校外工作？
00:08:55,830 - > 00:08:57,090
呃...
00:08:57,090 - > 00:09:01,160
这也很酷，因为当
您编写的代码和你似乎调试？
00:09:01,159 - > 00:09:04,568
环境，你可以把破发点
大约在同一个地方，从而导致很大
00:09:04,568 - > 00:09:07,579
凝聚力的环境，所有的权利
00:09:07,580 - > 00:09:11,980
去年，我还带了一个包
管理，但我捂住实物
00:09:11,980 - > 00:09:14,930
我要玩，暗示波浪方式
00:09:14,929 - > 00:09:16,089
包管理
00:09:16,090 - > 00:09:20,660
的东西，从现在起一年
我们要去有真正强大的软件包
00:09:20,659 - > 00:09:24,969
管理工具的基础设施和
很多包在社会权
00:09:24,970 - > 00:09:29,509
现在它是一种仍在寻找其
立足之地，但我们将看到一些更
00:09:29,509 - > 00:09:32,350
东西很快，我觉得
00:09:32,350 - > 00:09:37,350
是啊，嗯......实际上就在几个星期
发布前的凉亭
00:09:37,350 - > 00:09:39,778
凉亭的软件包管理项目
年初以来我一直在参与
00:09:39,778 - > 00:09:43,619
它真的被撤下奇妙
事情呃......在社区
00:09:43,619 - > 00:09:47,168
注册表样的吹起来这是一个
查看的所有组件
00:09:47,168 - > 00:09:51,199
凉亭和现在的
很少超过22百
00:09:51,200 - > 00:09:53,759
在注册表中的组件
00:09:53,759 - > 00:09:57,370
真正伟大的，你作为一个用户和
每当你想拉的东西
00:09:57,370 - > 00:09:59,470
它有它的伟大工程的依赖性
00:09:59,470 - > 00:10:02,629
也很大，因为它的生态系统
意味着我们能够建立在每个
00:10:02,629 - > 00:10:06,240
在一个有凝聚力的方式很多其他的工作
00:10:06,240 - > 00:10:08,570
如果你想要得到加快
有一个伟大的介绍一下
00:10:08,570 - > 00:10:12,650
凉亭两周前刚刚在谷歌IO
丹hoverd表现出了很多伟大的
00:10:12,649 - > 00:10:17,289
的东西，包括一个非常好的工作流程
也使用凉亭和requirejs的自耕农
00:10:17,289 - > 00:10:18,230
和咕噜
00:10:18,230 - > 00:10:21,570
创造这个伟大的使用经验
包管理的东西，你
00:10:21,570 - > 00:10:23,479
可能期望从另一种语言
00:10:23,479 - > 00:10:28,350
呃...但它里面
呃...前端的javascript
00:10:28,350 - > 00:10:32,220
好吧想回来性能
并在谈论性能
00:10:32,220 - > 00:10:33,199
javascript的会议
00:10:33,198 - > 00:10:36,149
呃...我可能会谈论的javascript
性能
00:10:36,149 - > 00:10:36,700
但它的
00:10:36,700 - > 00:10:38,990
好牢记
00:10:38,990 - > 00:10:40,470
JavaScript是不是
00:10:40,470 - > 00:10:41,519
样的
00:10:41,519 - > 00:10:43,480
它并不总是最好的目标
00:10:43,480 - > 00:10:47,800
这些幻灯片实际上是从
IE团队回来时，他们释放
00:10:47,799 - > 00:10:49,469
IE8
00:10:49,470 - > 00:10:53,620
但这个东西是真实的，是因为它是现在
00:10:53,620 - > 00:10:56,830
这里，我们接过来一看百强网站，看到哪里
00:10:56,830 - > 00:10:58,930
IE浏览器将时间花在
00:10:58,929 - > 00:11:00,958
仅有16％的时间花在
00:11:00,958 - > 00:11:02,149
在javascript
00:11:02,149 - > 00:11:06,169
休息，它在布局呈现格式
这里阿贾克斯重的网站，如
00:11:06,169 - > 00:11:10,349
javascript的重像呵... gmail的
谷歌地图
00:11:10,350 - > 00:11:13,350
呃...还只是一小部分
00:11:13,350 - > 00:11:16,759
这样的javascript往往是一个小
分数的整体性能
00:11:16,759 - > 00:11:17,700
图片
00:11:17,700 - > 00:11:19,819
所以，如果你想找出如何使
00:11:19,818 - > 00:11:22,039
您的应用程序的现场快
00:11:22,039 - > 00:11:25,409
我建议你​​看一看在时间轴
里面铬的开发工具，以便
00:11:25,409 - > 00:11:28,309
呃...我要表明你现在
00:11:28,309 - > 00:11:29,239
好的
00:11:29,240 - > 00:11:33,340
所以这是一种信息图形视差网站
00:11:33,340 - > 00:11:34,480
它很酷
00:11:34,480 - > 00:11:38,149
我只是要通过它滚动
你得到一个机会，看看会发生什么，因为我就这么
00:11:38,149 - > 00:11:43,319
向下滚动，我得到这个橙色
圆泡状的家伙，这些
00:11:43,320 - > 00:11:44,940
界这里来
00:11:44,940 - > 00:11:47,660
一些真棒物理学爆炸
00:11:47,659 - > 00:11:48,799
呃...
00:11:48,799 - > 00:11:53,229
然后来这里，我们具有视差
影响我继续下去，它很酷
00:11:53,230 - > 00:11:55,649
呃......继续下去
00:11:55,649 - > 00:11:59,870
这些白色的小圆点形成这些GRIDE的
刚接手的地方
00:11:59,870 - > 00:12:02,039
这就是它，所有的权利
00:12:02,039 - > 00:12:05,039
让我们回到并打开开发工具
00:12:05,039 - > 00:12:07,589
并将其向下拖动至底部
00:12:07,590 - > 00:12:09,990
开拓时间表
00:12:09,990 - > 00:12:12,100
我要开始录制
00:12:12,100 - > 00:12:13,329
刚刚打命令+ D
00:12:13,328 - > 00:12:15,139
这是一种快速
00:12:15,139 - > 00:12:19,809
然后我只是要去翻阅
同样的东西
00:12:19,809 - > 00:12:24,679
嘟嘟嘟嘟
00:12:24,679 - > 00:12:28,029
所有的权利，什么是真正酷
我们为您
00:12:28,029 - > 00:12:30,129
在本页面种表现
00:12:30,129 - > 00:12:31,269
叙述
00:12:31,269 - > 00:12:33,549
它开始了在开始的时候是相当的寒意
00:12:33,549 - > 00:12:36,649
然后我们转移到这里的部分
那里有很多绿色
00:12:36,649 - > 00:12:38,058
现在这是在顶部
00:12:38,058 - > 00:12:40,610
我们正在建设这种橙色
00:12:40,610 - > 00:12:45,039
爆炸的圆和绿色油漆中使用了的时间
00:12:45,039 - > 00:12:48,588
在这里，我们绘制整个
页面上的每一个帧
00:12:48,589 - > 00:12:50,430
它采取了良好的时间量
00:12:50,429 - > 00:12:53,120
然后进入本节中有很多黄色
00:12:53,120 - > 00:12:54,039
这是JavaScript的执行
00:12:54,039 - > 00:12:55,730
那就是当我们打
00:12:55,730 - > 00:12:58,940
呃...这个小的物理动作这里
00:12:58,940 - > 00:13:03,170
这是很安静的部分
在中间，我们打我们的目标
00:13:03,169 - > 00:13:06,250
60 fps的帧预算大多帧留底下的
00:13:06,250 - > 00:13:07,539
大多
00:13:07,539 - > 00:13:10,669
再往下的底部，我们种得
这种不协调的颜色
00:13:10,669 - > 00:13:13,919
发生了很多事情，这种
白色的东西爆炸
00:13:13,919 - > 00:13:18,860
呃...画javascript和也
一个良好的数额紫色的布局
00:13:18,860 - > 00:13:21,120
呃...是怎么回事
00:13:21,120 - > 00:13:24,659
但时间表给我们这个整体
发现我们的炸弹吗？
00:13:24,659 - > 00:13:27,860
每一部分，这样我们就可以处理有点
我们如何调整这些更精确
00:13:27,860 - > 00:13:29,110
性能问题
00:13:29,110 - > 00:13:30,810
所以如果我想看看
00:13:30,809 - > 00:13:36,319
本节就在这里，我要怎么做
让我们看看这里
00:13:36,320 - > 00:13:41,300
呃...我希望得到一个更好的主意
这个JavaScript性能
00:13:41,299 - > 00:13:43,490
让我们这样做
00:13:43,490 - > 00:13:48,919
我要去型材和收集的CPU配置文件
00:13:48,919 - > 00:13:51,789
命中命令+ E
00:13:51,789 - > 00:13:53,709
和
00:13:53,710 - > 00:13:54,970
它可能是好
00:13:54,970 - > 00:13:58,470
现在如果我来这里，呃......
00:13:58,470 - > 00:14:00,480
所以这一点，你应使用
00:14:00,480 - > 00:14:03,450
一种聚合视图一切是怎么回事
00:14:03,450 - > 00:14:08,320
它告诉我这里种有
所有发生的事情信息
00:14:08,320 - > 00:14:10,010
以及它没有做什么
00:14:10,009 - > 00:14:13,559
把它给我那种这一观点
我可以看到一帧一帧
00:14:13,559 - > 00:14:16,959
发生了什么事有点位
00:14:16,960 - > 00:14:20,110
所以这是我们发现我们可以
地址，也给你一个更好的主意
00:14:20,110 - > 00:14:20,919
据
00:14:20,919 - > 00:14:22,748
这个动作的可视化
00:14:22,749 - > 00:14:25,279
所以我想告诉你一个新的功能
00:14:25,279 - > 00:14:29,019
这就是所谓的火焰图
00:14:29,019 - > 00:14:29,990
呃......所有权利
00:14:29,990 - > 00:14:32,279
所以在这里，我们有火焰图
00:14:32,279 - > 00:14:36​​,759
我们能够找出一种
事物是如何跨越时间的时间尺度
00:14:36​​,759 - > 00:14:39,629
在这种情况下，改变它实际上是相当一致的
00:14:39,629 - > 00:14:43,189
嗯...看起来就像是一帧一帧
主要执行相同的JavaScript
00:14:43,190 - > 00:14:44,820
它会改变颜色，如果不
00:14:44,820 - > 00:14:46,290
呃...然后也
00:14:46,289 - > 00:14:49,709
所以这是一个特定的帧钻
00:14:49,710 - > 00:14:50,790
和
00:14:50,789 - > 00:14:53,009
在这种情况下，呃......
00:14:53,009 - > 00:14:53,889
宽度是时间
00:14:53,889 - > 00:14:57,179
和高度的调用堆栈，所以高度不是太重要
00:14:57,179 - > 00:14:58,339
不过呢
00:14:58,340 - > 00:15:0​​2,460
如果我想看看我能看到几件事情，让我们说
00:15:0​​2,460 - > 00:15:0​​4,030
呃...这里
00:15:0​​4,029 - > 00:15:0​​7,429
看起来像D3是一种运行
展示我所有的时间花在内部D3
00:15:0​​7,429 - > 00:15:0​​8,419
00:15:0​​8,419 - > 00:15:12,779
我们得到了一些插入的孩子，所以它做了一些SVG插入
00:15:12,779 - > 00:15:19,240
呃...然后我们有这个四叉树视图
四叉树视图四叉树视图四叉树视图
插入子
00:15:19,240 - > 00:15:23,110
也插入属性功能
设置新属性，SVG
00:15:23,110 - > 00:15:24,600
在帧结束
00:15:24,600 - > 00:15:27,960
这是在这种情况下，一个七毫秒
这是一个相当长的时间
00:15:27,960 - > 00:15:29,720
发生的每一个帧
00:15:29,720 - > 00:15:33,600
但这种可视化给了我一个伟大的观点了，因为它浸泡了这
00:15:33,600 - > 00:15:37,790
首先，我应该怎么解决
00:15:37,789 - > 00:15:39,659
所以这是新的火烧图表
00:15:39,659 - > 00:15:41,699
你可以检查它在今天铬金丝雀
00:15:41,700 - > 00:15:46,090
呃...我们也有一个帆布分析
我想告诉你现在的实验
00:15:46,090 - > 00:15:51,850
所以这里只是这个WebGL的水族馆
伊马打开开发工具
00:15:51,850 - > 00:15:56,779
并采取帆布配置文件，所以它的
要记录单帆布框架和
00:15:56,779 - > 00:16:00,500
它记录所有的呼叫
促成该帧
00:16:00,500 - > 00:16:04,129
并捅所有抽奖电话
一个接一个，只是击中的向下箭头
00:16:04,129 - > 00:16:06,090
在键盘上穿行
00:16:06,090 - > 00:16:09,360
场面实际上是如何绘制的，所以你可以看到
00:16:09,360 - > 00:16:11,820
鱼和鲨鱼
00:16:11,820 - > 00:16:15,670
进来的球种
和其他一切
00:16:15,669 - > 00:16:18,639
然后你打开抽奖电话
并看到所有的函数调用
00:16:18,639 - > 00:16:20,259
贡献，平局
00:16:20,259 - > 00:16:21,950
回去来源
00:16:21,950 - > 00:16:26,210
所以这是很酷，但是这是一个平台，
这是我们能够记录和重放
00:16:26,210 - > 00:16:28,120
帆布和WebGL的行动
00:16:28,120 - > 00:16:30,568
呃...但真的，我们从这里走
00:16:30,568 - > 00:16:34,358
是你的，所以请扳手
那种你将您的反馈意见
00:16:34,359 - > 00:16:38,889
喜欢看未来尽可能画布分析器
00:16:38,889 - > 00:16:42,649
没事，我会总结了五个关键
开发工具的性能特点
00:16:42,649 - > 00:16:44,970
首先连续重绘模式
00:16:44,970 - > 00:16:49,009
如果你在时间轴上，你看到了很多
绿色绘画里面度过的时间
00:16:49,009 - > 00:16:51,850
那么你可能想在T头
连续重绘模式，它会做什么
00:16:51,850 - > 00:16:52,999
是告诉浏览器
00:16:52,999 - > 00:16:55,759
哎一遍又一遍画页
00:16:55,759 - > 00:16:58,730
这是什么让你做的是关闭的元素和风格
00:16:58,730 - > 00:17:01,789
弄清楚什么是贡献
的时间量，它需要画
00:17:01,789 - > 00:17:02,769
的页面
00:17:02,769 - > 00:17:06,709
呃...这是能够呵...让
你发现了什么贡献你
00:17:06,709 - > 00:17:11,230
可以调整呃......它的变化，使
这是一个这是一个有点艰难的
00:17:11,230 - > 00:17:12,470
给定的聚合视图
00:17:12,470 - > 00:17:15,329
但你能找出到底
有什么贡献
00:17:15,329 - > 00:17:19,269
FPS仪表嗯...哪
给你一个很好的观点，你的速度有多快
00:17:19,269 - > 00:17:21,029
发送对屏幕的更新
00:17:21,029 - > 00:17:24,930
所以除了显示帧每秒
我们也有在该视图中的最小值和最大值
00:17:24,930 - > 00:17:26,110
及直方图
00:17:26,109 - > 00:17:29,298
也是GPU的内存，所以你可以看到有多少内存
00:17:29,298 - > 00:17:33,388
正在使用的当前选项卡，如何
多少是分配的，如果你有很多
00:17:33,388 - > 00:17:36,308
你要不断的重意象
驱逐的GPU
00:17:36,308 - > 00:17:40,930
这可能是我泡了一个良好的数额GPU性能的内存
00:17:40,930 - > 00:17:45,140
呃...下显示涂料矩形的层边界
这些都可以作为设置里面
00:17:45,140 - > 00:17:45,969
开发工具
00:17:45,969 - > 00:17:49,940
真正伟大的识别涂料
所以你可能会重新粉刷的问题
00:17:49,940 - > 00:17:52,750
对每一个滚动整个页面
00:17:52,750 - > 00:17:55,779
你不wannna做到这一点，这是
要告诉你一个可视化的视图
00:17:55,779 - > 00:17:58,979
在这种情况下发生的真快呵...
它看起来像
00:17:58,979 - > 00:18:01,058
这个div刚刚粉刷的，我们有
00:18:01,058 - > 00:18:04,569
呃...在这里一层金色边框
00:18:04,569 - > 00:18:08,500
它实际上是滚动
铬的复合右
00:18:08,500 - > 00:18:11,210
页面顶部的
00:18:11,210 - > 00:18:14,890
对象分配纤夫品牌
新的工具，如果你正在做大量的内存
00:18:14,890 - > 00:18:18,440
分析这是怎么回事你这么关键
你打一个做记录，它是要花
00:18:18,440 - > 00:18:24,490
随着时间的推移不断堆快照
它是如何识别一个特定的部分drillin
00:18:24,490 - > 00:18:28,240
看什么样的对象被分配在该节
00:18:28,240 - > 00:18:31,250
他们保留大小和他们
护树，这是伟大甚至尝试
00:18:31,250 - > 00:18:35,240
确定你的记忆
从到哪里去
00:18:35,240 - > 00:18:40,190
最后布局颠簸呃...
这里这个时间表
00:18:40,190 - > 00:18:43,470
我们看到了大量的时间花费在
布局
00:18:43,470 - > 00:18:47,519
在这里，我们就能够识别出
一堆东​​西，你有一个DOM重
00:18:47,519 - > 00:18:49,210
Web应用程序
00:18:49,210 - > 00:18:53,170
你可能会看到这样的事情在哪里
你在做布局的布局和布局
00:18:53,170 - > 00:18:56,410
你做这一切有没有油漆
工作，你问的浏览器做这一切
00:18:56,410 - > 00:18:57,220
工作
00:18:57,220 - > 00:19:02,100
用户从来没有见过它的很多
开发工具是要去的，这是一个问题
00:19:02,099 - > 00:19:06,000
告诉你，有这个小图标
可能出现的性能瓶颈
00:19:06,000 - > 00:19:09,730
呃...这也是我给你
过了很多其他有用的信息
00:19:09,730 - > 00:19:13,500
量需要布局的节点
树的大小范围
00:19:13,500 - > 00:19:18,150
，也是一个完整的调用堆栈为什么
布局是无效的，为什么它被迫
00:19:18,150 - > 00:19:22,030
联合分析功能，并准确地找到
为什么事情引起的，也许你会需要
00:19:22,029 - > 00:19:24,119
改变一些东西左右
00:19:24,119 - > 00:19:27,639
所以很多的细节，这是获得良好的网络性能的关键
00:19:27,640 - > 00:19:29,299
应用程序
00:19:29,298 - > 00:19:33,420
好吧，这是一个很多东西铬工具文档
最近有一堆
00:19:33,420 - > 00:19:37,070
新的更新，涵盖这些东西
和一堆包括远程
00:19:37,069 - > 00:19:41,829
调试一切，我今天呃...
可远程调试
00:19:41,829 - > 00:19:46,308
手机呃......所以这是一个真正强大
设置和我鼓励你检查出来
00:19:46,308 - > 00:19:50,259
呃...一切，我今天应该也是
他们中的一些背后的金丝雀
00:19:50,259 - > 00:19:54,220
实验，但我鼓励你去看看
尝试的事情发牢骚我，告诉我什么
00:19:54,220 - > 00:19:57,860
你喜欢什么你不喜欢呵......和
呃...它会是不错
00:19:57,859 - > 00:19:58,629
但谢谢你们非常